(Sheldon:)...to attend her aunt's tedious
birthday party.
- Not a chance.
- All right.
l thought the candy might not
be enough, so let me up the ante.
Ahem. These are Cooper Coupons.
(Sheldon:)These are for various things
l can do for you.
(Sheldon:)Um, oh, this one is for
one free grammar check.
(Stuart:)Uh...
(Sheldon:)You could use it for e-mails,
letters, tattoos, what have you.
(Stuart:)Uh...
Oh, this is a fun one.
This is an afternoon with me...
(Sheldon:)...at the California Science Center
where I point out their mistakes.
(Leonard:)Keep an eye on those expiration dates.
l've been burned more than once.
I'm not gonna get involved
in your relationship.
Come on. It's just a simple favor.
When's the last time...
- ...l asked you to do something for me?
- Yesterday.
(Penny:)You made me look in your ear
to see if there was a ladybug in it.
(Sheldon:)Last time I asked you to do something
that wasn't a medical emergency?
(Penny:)Yesterday. You made me look in your ear
to see if there was a ladybug in it.